

Garabajiu Alexandra

LinkedIn URL: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandra-garabajiu-ivanova/

E-mail: garabajiualexandra27091991@gmail.com

Phone: +373 60 36 62 65

Address: mun. Chisinau, Durlesti sity, str. Atelierilor 4

Personal details

Date of birth: September 27th, 1991

Gender: Female Civil status: married

Children: 2

Languages

Russian – native Romanian – advanced English - intermediate Ukrainian - intermediate French - beginner

Summary

I'm a highly motivated professional person with technical education launching career as a Quality Assurance engineer. My practice experience in manual testing is limited by Functional and Usability Interface testing on freelance platform Utest. I am a person, who perform various tasks very well and I'm always open to new knowledge. I am not afraid of difficulties and new ideas because I am a leader, with creative and organizational skills, who knows how to achieve the goal and believes in what I do! I am also a supporter of consistency, clear tasks and deadlines. With me, you will never lose anything.

Courses

Tekwill Academy (Aug 2022 - Dec 2022) - QA Manual Tasting

- Fundamentals of testing
- SDLC methodologies
- Test Documentation (Plan, Checl-list, Tast case)
- Testing design techniques
- Agile Methodology
- Web/mobile testing
- Jira, TestRail, Confluence, DevTools, Catalon Studio, Basics of SQL and Gherkin Scenario for testing purposes

Personal Skills

- Attention to detail and multitasking
- Capable for analyzing and solving problems
- Strong leadership and organizational skills

<u>Internship</u>

QA Manual tester in mobile

Dec 2022

AppCake

- Mobile testing in Unity and iOS projects (native applications and mods for games)
- UI testing, Usability/UX testing, Functional testing, Exploratory testing, End2End testing
- Bag reporting (Detection of Severity)
- Jira, Slack, Vysor, xCode

Employment

Freelance Manual tester

Aug 2022 – present

https://www.utest.com/

- UI testing, Usability/UX testing, Functional testing, Exploratory testing, Web testing
- Bag reporting (Detection of Severity and Priority)

Content management

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

SRL Admix

- Site and social-media administration
- Copywriting/Translations

Project manager

Sept 2020 - Jun 2021

SRL "SimulSHOP" (Charity Shop "SHOPMesto"), Chisinau

- Administration of project "MESTO razdachi veshei"
- Organization of internal process, documentation and reporting
- Public relations and socially useful activity
- Negotiating with different local authorities, public organizations, social workers

Sales consultant

Oct 2019 - Jun 2021

SRL "SimulSHOP" (Charity Shop "SHOPMesto"), Chisinau

- Direct sales
- Build and maintain relationships with clients
- Introduced new customers to the charity shop system

Volunteer department coordinator

May 2019 - Sep 2020

Charitable Foundation "Klub Dobryakov", Moscow

- Crowd Funding for sick children
- Organization of treatment for sick children in foreign clinics
- Development, coordination and implementation of socially useful projects in collaboration with different public organizations
- Organization of different activities for sick children
- Negotiating, searching for new partners and sponsors, communicating with the press

<u>Senior sales manager</u>

Jan 2016 - Sep 2019

SRL "PLASTAL", Chisinau

- Organization and improvement of internal processes, quality control of the product and provided services
- Selling company products (premium PVC windows and doors), B2B B2C sales
- Build and maintain relationships with clients, preparation of commercial offers and negotiation
- Trainings of new personal
- Project development taking into account engineering requirements

Superior analyst

Sep 2014 - Dec 2015

State Agrarian University of Moldova (Department of Territory Organization), Chisinau

- Preparation of educational material and practical training of students
- Management and internal document flow, meeting minutes

Trainings

2022 Tekwill Academy , Chisinau – Soft skills

2019 Charitable Foundation "Club dobrykov", Moscow - Soft communications, Team building, Public speaking

Educational Background

State Agrarian University of Moldova, Chisinau

Faculty Cadastry and Law

Master Degree of Architecture and Construction

Sept 2010 - Dec 2015